https://www.fangraphs.com/about/privacy-policy

What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how Fangraphs treats personal information that Fangraphs collects
and receives, including information related to your past use of Fangraphs products
and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable
like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise
publicly available.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Fangraphs does not
own or control, or to people that Fangraphs does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
Fangraphs collects personal information when you register with Fangraphs, when you
use Fangraphs products or services, when you visit Fangraphs pages or the pages
of certain Fangraphs partners. Fangraphs may combine information about you that
we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth
date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register
with Fangraphs and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
Fangraphs collects information about your transactions with us and with some of
our business partners.
Fangraphs automatically receives and records information on our server logs from
your browser, including your IP address, Fangraphs cookie information, and the page
you request.
Fangraphs uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the
advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services,
improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting
for internal and external clients.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Fangraphs does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other
people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've
requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Fangraphs
under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information
to help Fangraphs communicate with you about offers from Fangraphs and our marketing
partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this
information.
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise
our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent,
or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving
potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Fangraphs's
terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if Fangraphs is acquired by or merged with another
company. In this event, Fangraphs will notify you before information about you is
transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Fangraphs displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers
(including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view,
or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24
from a particular geographic area.
Fangraphs does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact
with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are
consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that
you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
Fangraphs advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance
agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as
stores, airlines, and software companies).
Cookies
Fangraphs may set and access Fangraphs cookies on your computer.
Fangraphs lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set
and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies
is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies
do not have access to Fangraphs's cookies.
Fangraphs uses web beacons to access Fangraphs cookies inside and outside our network
of web sites and in connection with Fangraphs products and services.
Third Party Advertisers
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type,
time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements
about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These
companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to
opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
You can edit your Fangraphs Account Information including your marketing preferences
(when available), at any time.
New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences
page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future
marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following
instructions contained in the messages they receive.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Fangraphs
service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Fangraphs
Newsletter, that are considered part of your Fangraphs account, without offering
you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably
need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services
to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal
regulations to protect personal information about you.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Fangraphs may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in
the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address
specified in your Fangraphs account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form.
Updated: Thursday, December 10, 2020 10:50 AM ETUpdated: 12/10/2020 10:50 AM ET
Player Linker - Contact Us - Advertise
- Terms of Service - Privacy Policy
All major league baseball data including pitch type, velocity, batted ball location,
and play-by-play data provided by Baseball Info Solutions.
Major League and Minor League Baseball data provided by Major League Baseball.
Mitchel Lichtman
All UZR (ultimate zone rating) calculations are provided courtesy of Mitchel Lichtman.
TangoTiger.com
All Win Expectancy, Leverage Index, Run Expectancy, and Fans Scouting Report data licenced from TangoTiger.com
Retrosheet.org
Play-by-play data prior to 2002 was obtained free of charge from and is copyrighted
by Retrosheet.
